{
    "subject": "resource/Jill_Ker_Conway",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Australia",
    "human_readable": "Jill Ker Conway was born in Australia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9713723063468933,
            "question": "Did Jill Ker Conway grow up in Australia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9415069818496704,
            "question": "Is Jill Ker Conway Australian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8893349170684814,
            "question": "Where was Jill Ker Conway born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7636085748672485,
            "question": "Is Jill Ker Conway's birthplace known?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6511253118515015,
            "question": "Was Jill Ker Conway born in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5686479210853577,
            "question": "What country is Jill Ker Conway from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38886043429374695,
            "question": "What is Jill Ker Conway famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3378125727176666,
            "question": "Is there any other information available about Jill Ker Conway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28785252571105957,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Jill Ker Conway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10628661513328552,
            "question": "What continent is Australia located on?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jill Ker Conway was born in Australia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2692_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Jill Ker Conway?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2692_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other information available about Jill Ker Conway?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2692_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Jill Ker Conway famous for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2692_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2692_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple \"Jill Ker Conway was born in Australia\". Specifically, document 1 and 5 mention that Jill Ker Conway was born in Hillston, New South Wales, Australia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis answer is based on the provided documents, which state that Jill Ker Conway was born in Hillston, New South Wales, Australia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}